<root>
    <Unpair>

        <trans-unit id="COMM_UnpairMeterHdr">
			<croatian>Prekinuti vezu s ovim glukometrom?</croatian>
			<danish>Slet forbindelse til apparatet?</danish>
			<dutch>Meter ontkoppelen?</dutch>
			<english>Unpair Meter?</english>
			<finnish>Poistetaanko yhteys mittariin?</finnish>
			<french>Déjumeler le lecteur ?</french>
			<german>Messgerät abkoppeln?</german>
			<greek>Αποσύζευξη Μετρητή;</greek>
			<italian>Dissociare lo strumento?</italian>
			<norwegian>Oppheve paring av måler?</norwegian>
			<polish>Anulować synchronizację glukometru?</polish>
			<portugal>Desemparelhar o medidor?</portugal>
			<slovenian>Preklic povezave z merilnikom?</slovenian>
			<spanish>¿Desvincular medidor?</spanish>
			<swedish>Ta bort parkoppling för mätare?</swedish>
		</trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="COMM_unpairingInfo">
			<croatian>
			Jeste li sigurni da želite prekinuti vezu ovog glukometra sa svojim računom? Prethodno sinkronizirana očitanja šećera u krvi ostat će na vašem računu. Buduća očitanja neće biti sinkronizirana s računom.
			</croatian>
			<danish>
			Er du sikker på at du vil afbryde forbindelsen til apparatet fra din konto? Tidligere synkroniserede målinger forbliver på kontoen. Fremtidige målinger synkroniseres ikke til kontoen.
			</danish>
			<dutch>
			Weet u zeker dat u deze meter wilt ontkoppelen van uw account? Eerder gesynchroniseerde resultaten blijven op uw account staan. Toekomstige resultaten worden niet naar het account gesynchroniseerd.
			</dutch>
			<english>
			Are you sure you want to unpair this meter from your account? Previously synced readings will remain on your account. Future readings will not be synced to the account.
			</english>
			<finnish>
			Haluatko varmasti poistaa yhteyden tähän mittariin tilistäsi? Aiemmin synkronoidut tulokset pysyvät tililläsi. Tulevia tuloksia ei synkronoida tilille.
			</finnish>
			<french>
			Voulez-vous vraiment déjumeler ce lecteur de votre compte ? Les résultats précédemment synchronisés resteront sur votre compte. Les résultats à venir ne seront pas synchronisés avec le compte.
			</french>
			<german>
			Möchten Sie dieses Messgerät wirklich von Ihrem Konto abkoppeln? Zuvor synchronisierte Messwerte bleiben in Ihrem Konto. Künftige Messwerte werden nicht mit dem Konto synchronisiert.
			</german>
			<greek>
			Είστε σίγουροι ότι θέλετε να διακόψετε τη σύζευξη αυτού του μετρητή από τον λογαριασμό σας; Οι προηγούμενες μετρήσεις θα παραμείνουν στον λογαριασμό σας αλλά οι μελλοντικές δεν θα συγχρονιστούν.
			</greek>
			<italian>
			Vuoi dissociare questo strumento dal tuo account? I risultati sincronizzati in precedenza resteranno sul tuo account. I prossimi risultati non verranno sincronizzati con l\\\'account.
			</italian>
			<norwegian>
			Er du sikker på at du vil oppheve paringen av denne måleren med kontoen din? Tidligere synkroniserte målinger blir værende på kontoen. Fremtidige målinger blir ikke synkronisert med kontoen.
			</norwegian>
			<polish>
			Czy na pewno chcesz anulować synchronizację tego glukometru z konta? Poprzednio uzgodnione wyniki pozostaną na Twoim koncie. Dalsze wyniki nie będą uzgadniane z kontem.
			</polish>
			<portugal>
			Deseja mesmo desemparelhar este medidor da sua conta? As leituras previamente sincronizadas permanecerão na sua conta. Futuras leituras não serão sincronizadas com a conta.
			</portugal>
			<slovenian>
			Res želite preklicati povezavo tega merilnika s svojim računom? Predhodno sinhronizirane izmerjene vrednosti bodo ostale na vašem računu. Prihodnje izmerjene vrednosti ne bodo sinhronizirane z računom.
			</slovenian>
			<spanish>
			¿Seguro que desea desvincular este medidor de su cuenta? Las lecturas sincronizadas anteriormente permanecerán en su cuenta. Las lecturas futuras no se sincronizarán con la cuenta.
			</spanish>
			<swedish>
			Är du säker på att du vill ta bort parkopplingen för denna mätare från ditt konto? Tidigare synkroniserade värden är kvar på ditt konto. Framtida värden kommer inte att synkroniseras med kontot.
			</swedish>
		</trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="COMM_UnpairBtn">
			<croatian>Prekini vezu</croatian>
			<danish>Afbryd forbindelse.</danish>
			<dutch>Ontkoppelen</dutch>
			<english>Unpair</english>
			<finnish>Poista yhteys</finnish>
			<french>Déjumeler</french>
			<german>Abkoppeln</german>
			<greek>Αποσύζευξη</greek>
			<italian>Dissociare</italian>
			<norwegian>Opphev paring</norwegian>
			<polish>Rozłącz</polish>
			<portugal>Desemparelhar</portugal>
			<slovenian>Prekliči povezavo</slovenian>
			<spanish>Eliminar</spanish>
			<swedish>Ta bort parkoppling</swedish>
		</trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="COMM_cancelbtn">
			<croatian>Otkaži</croatian>
			<danish>Annullér</danish>
			<dutch>Annuleer</dutch>
			<english>Cancel</english>
			<finnish>Peruuta</finnish>
			<french>Annuler</french>
			<german>Abbrechen</german>
			<greek>Ακύρωση</greek>
			<italian>Annulla</italian>
			<norwegian>Avbryt</norwegian>
			<polish>Anuluj</polish>
			<portugal>Cancelar</portugal>
			<slovenian>Prekliči</slovenian>
			<spanish>Cancelar</spanish>
			<swedish>Avbryt</swedish>
		</trans-unit>
    </Unpair>
	<Delete>
		   <trans-unit id="COMM_UnpairBtn">
			<croatian>Prekini vezu</croatian>
			<danish>Afbryd forbindelse.</danish>
			<dutch>Ontkoppelen</dutch>
			<english>Unpair</english>
			<finnish>Poista yhteys</finnish>
			<french>Déjumeler</french>
			<german>Abkoppeln</german>
			<greek>Αποσύζευξη</greek>
			<italian>Dissociare</italian>
			<norwegian>Opphev paring</norwegian>
			<polish>Rozłącz</polish>
			<portugal>Desemparelhar</portugal>
			<slovenian>Prekliči povezavo</slovenian>
			<spanish>Eliminar</spanish>
			<swedish>Ta bort parkoppling</swedish>

		</trans-unit>
	</Delete>

</root>
